Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Percussionist Daniel Druckman and cellist Chris Finckel rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0247.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_063.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0254.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_064.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0255.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_065.tif)
- Pianist Adam Sherkin performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Adam Sherkin pianist.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_066.tif)
- Pianist Adam Sherkin performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Adam Sherkin John Adams American Berserk (2001).tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_067.tif)
- Pianist Adam Sherkin performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0264.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_068.tif)
- Pianist Adam Sherkin performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-05-31, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Adam Sherkin Performance Institute Concert.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_069.tif)
- Composer and flutist Harvey Sollberger at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0277.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_070.tif)
- Composer and flutist Harvey Sollberger at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0278.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_071.tif)
- Composer and flutist Harvey Sollberger at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Harvey Sollberger.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_072.tif)
- Composer David Felder presenting lecture to participants at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0292.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_073.tif)
- Audience of participants at June in Buffalo 2015 lecture by David Felder, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0293.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_074.tif)
- Composer David Felder presenting lecture to participants at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0295.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_075.tif)
- Composer David Felder presenting lecture to participants at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0296.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_076.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger talking with June in Buffalo 2015 participants James Romig and Ashlee Mack, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0306.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_077.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick during a presentation at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0315.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_078.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick during a presentation at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0321.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_079.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky (in blue jacket) during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0341.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_080.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky (in blue jacket) during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0342.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_081.tif)
- Composer Martin Bresnick during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0343.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_082.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0344.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_083.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0348.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_084.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0349.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_085.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Michael Lipsey, Matthew Gold, Ian Antonio, and Matt Ward with June in Buffalo 2015 student Lisa Eleazarian, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0351.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_086.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Michael Lipsey, Matthew Gold, Ian Antonio, and Matt Ward with June in Buffalo 2015 student Lisa Eleazarian, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0352.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_087.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matthew Gold, Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, and Matt Ward, conducted by Michael Lipsey performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0353.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_088.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matthew Gold, Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, Matt Ward, and Michael Lipsey after a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0361.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_089.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matthew Gold, Ian Antonio, Tom Kolor, Matt Ward, and Michael Lipsey applauding the composer Tiange Zhou after a performance of her Beginning of origin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0362.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_090.tif)
- Nicholas Emmanuel, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, Anna Whistler, Benjamin Havey, Hangyu Bai, and Adam Sherkin rehearsing Steve Reich's Six Pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0363.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_091.tif)
- Nicholas Emmanuel, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, Anna Whistler, Benjamin Havey, Hangyu Bai, and Adam Sherkin rehearsing Steve Reich's Six Pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0364.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_092.tif)
- Nicholas Emmanuel, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, Anna Whistler, Benjamin Havey, Hangyu Bai, and Adam Sherkin rehearsing Steve Reich's Six Pianos with faculty member Eric Huebner at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0369.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_093.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a performance by the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0370.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_094.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a performance by the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0371.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_095.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a performance by the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0372.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_096.tif)
- New York New Music Ensemble members Jean Kopperud, Stephen Gosling, Daniel Druckman, and Chris Finckel performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0373.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_097.tif)
- New York New Music Ensemble members Jean Kopperud, Stephen Gosling, Daniel Druckman, and Chris Finckel performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0375.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_098.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting a performance by the New York New Music Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0379.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_099.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro onstage with members of the New York New Music Ensemble Chris Finckel, cello, Stephen Gosling, piano, Mike Truesdell, percussion, Curtis Macomber, violin, Jean Kopperud, clarinet, and Emi Ferguson, flute after a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0382.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_100.tif)
- Composer Charles Wuorinen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Charles Wuorinen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_101.tif)
- Composers David Felder, Martin Bresnick, Harvey Sollberger, and Charles Wuorinen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name DavidFelder.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_102.tif)
- Composers David Felder, Martin Bresnick, Harvey Sollberger, and Charles Wuorinen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name David Felder Martin Bresnick Harvey Sollenberger Charles Wuorinen.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_103.tif)
- Composers David Felder and Martin Bresnick with clarinetist Jean Kopperud at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-01, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0393.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_104.tif)
- Flutist Wayla Chambo at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0395.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_105.tif)
- Flutist Wayla Chambo with composer David Nguyen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0398.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_106.tif)
- Flutist Wayla Chambo with composer David Nguyen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0399.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_107.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0403.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_108.tif)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Liliya Ugay, and cellist T. J. Borden rehearsing Ugay's Third world fable at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0407.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_109.tif)
- Violinist Yuki Numata Resnick, pianist Liliya Ugay, and cellist T. J. Borden rehearsing Ugay's Third world fable at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0408.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_110.tif)
- Percussionists Tom Kolor and Ian Antonio rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0410.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_111.tif)
- Percussionists Tom Kolor and Ian Antonio rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0412.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_112.tif)
- Percussionists Tom Kolor and Ian Antonio rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0414.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_113.tif)
- Percussionists Tom Kolor and Ian Antonio rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0418.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_114.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0422.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_115.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Stucky.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_116.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds with violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0430.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_117.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0432.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_118.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Arditti.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_119.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Irvine Arditti.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_120.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0434.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_121.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds with violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0439.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_122.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds with violinist Irvine Arditti at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0440.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_123.tif)
- Percussionists Ian Antonio and Tom Kolor rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0442.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_124.tif)
- Meridian Arts Ensemble members Tim Leopold, Benjamin Herrington, Raymond Stewart, Daniel Grabois, and Jon Nelson performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0444.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_125.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble, conducted by Tom Kolor, rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0445.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_126.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matthew Gold, Matt Ward, Ian Antonio, and Michael Lipsey rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0446.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_127.tif)
- Talujon Percussion Ensemble members Matthew Gold and Michael Lipsey rehearsing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0447.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_128.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky at a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0448.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_129.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky (blue jacket) at a rehearsal with members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0449.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_130.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky (blue jacket) at a rehearsal with members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0450.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_131.tif)
- Composer Steven Stucky (blue jacket) at a rehearsal with members of the Talujon Percussion Ensemble at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0452.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_132.tif)
- Meridian Arts Ensemble members Tim Leopold, Benjamin Herrington, Raymond Stewart, Daniel Grabois, and Jon Nelson performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0454.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_133.tif)
- Meridian Arts Ensemble members Tim Leopold, Benjamin Herrington, Raymond Stewart, Daniel Grabois, and Jon Nelson performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0461.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_134.tif)
- Percussionist Bill Solomon performing Brian Ferneyhough's Bone alphabet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0468.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_135.tif)
- Percussionist Bill Solomon performing Brian Ferneyhough's Bone alphabet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0469.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_136.tif)
- Percussionist Bill Solomon performing Brian Ferneyhough's Bone alphabet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0470.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_137.tif)
- Composer Brian Ferneyhough applauding the performance of his Bone alphabet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0479.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_138.tif)
- Composer Brian Ferneyhough applauding the performance of his Bone alphabet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 black and white digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0480.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_139.tif)
- Tom Kolor conducting a performance by the Talujon Percussion Ensemble with timpanist John Smigielski at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0481.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_140.tif)